One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
Let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
Groggy Ring!!
Our mighty Groggy Ring
combatants have taken the field!
Opposing them...
...is the violent cook who kicked
the interference squads'
butt in Round One; Sanji!
That's "first-rate cook."
And the pirate hunter with a bounty
of 60 million; Roronoa Zoro!
This is what they called us
out here for? What a laugh!
Right Big Pan?
Huh?
He can't hear ya.
What's with these guys?
We'll start with a coin toss.
Tails.
Field or ball?
Ball.
Our Groggy Monsters have chosen the ball!
The Straw Hat ball man will
enter the other team's mid-circle!
Which side do you want?
Doesn't matter.
During the game there are two
"ball men" with a ball on their heads!
Knock your opponent's ball man into your opponent's ring and you win!
Just get on with it!
Get in position ball man!
Hey now.
I don't care how pushy you are.
I still ain't gonna be the damn ball.
I refuse to wear this stupid thing!
Quit your whining!
Oh! Looks good on you!
I won't fall for that moron!
Zoro! Sanji! It's up to you guys!
Win Chopper back! We can't lose now!
I'm really sorry! We're counting on you!
Whoa a wotan... I've never seen one before!
I guess they're not as large
as pureblooded giants.
Cheer them on all you
want; it's still no use!
Everyone on our team is a Groggy Ring expert!
What do you want Split-Head?
He said it again...
Oh, Boss!
Now quit doing that Straw Hat!
I doubt I'll need to interfere with this game,
so I thought I'd watch too.
Got a problem with that?
Interference is allowed with this game too?!
Imbecile! It's allowed for every game!
It's just some people will stoop to anything to help their team win
while others might insist on a
fair-and-square contest, you know?
So it depends on the situation.
But if you can't even
handle a little interference
how can you hope to survive
as a seafaring pirate?
It's a question of character.
That's how you justify it?
What's with that team of yours anyway?!
If you can even call it a team!
Talk all you want! Once the match starts
you'll see what they can--!
You went too early just now!
Did not! I win!
At everything.
Don't be a smartass!
We're talking about rock-paper-scissors here!
No you lost!
Just decide on a ball man already!
They haven't even agreed on that yet...
Sanji-kun! That ball looks nice on you!
I'll do it! I'm the ball man! I'm the worthiest!
It does suit you. You look like a prince.
Of Moronica.
Just start the game!
Hold on! Weapons are against the rules! Lose the swords!
Huh? Really?
Yes this is a ball game!
It wouldn't be much of a game if weapons were allowed!
I'm fine either way to be honest!
Hey you gonna be okay?
A master swordsman without swords is...
Is what?
...nothing but a worthless wimp.
Knock it off you guys!
All right! It's now or never!
The Straw Hats' ball man Sanji has entered the opponent's circle!
Hey cook, I hope you get trampled.
Shut up!
Stomp 'im Big Pan!
The crowd is all fired up!
Big Pan! Let's run-and-gun 'em!
Huh?
He can't hear ya!
U-Uhh...
C'mon man...
Pay attention!
It's not that funny is it?
The Groggy Monsters are as jolly as always!
Let's get this delightful show on the road!
There's no time limit
and the first team to score wins!
So we win if we knock Jumbo's
head into the other ring...
And we lose if the cook's head
gets knocked into our ring...
Can Team Straw Hat win back
the reindeer they lost in Round One?!
Crush 'em!
Or will Team Foxy swipe
another crew member?!
They're about to clash in Groggy Ring!
The whistle is about to sound!
Let the game begin!
What will ball man Sanji do in enemy territory?!
Will he retreat or attack?!
Let's do it!
There goes "Tackle Machine" Pickles!
All right. I'll take care of this myself.
Sling Tackle!
I don't care about you!
I'm only after you!
All we gotta do to win is beat you down!
It's a ball man battle!
Collier...!
Wh-What the...?! His skin's all slimy!
Sanji the cook slips and slides
on Big Pan's outstretched arm!
It's only natural though...
...for Big Pan is a slippery-skinned
wotan of loach origin!
What the heck are you doing?!
Run-and-gun!
You idiot!
Who are you calling an idiot?!
Punk Pass!
There it is! Big Pan's super-long pass!
Sanji!
Their leader Hamburg
makes for the landing point!
With Roronoa Zoro racing by his side!
I'll chop you up if they score a goal!
Shut up! Quit your whining!
Sweeping Tackle!
Pickles enters enemy territory!
Meanwhile can Hamburg
catch Sanji in the air?!
Yes! And then...!
Gorilla Throw!
I got it! I got it!
Waiting for him now is Pickles!
Get back here! I'll teach you to...!
Roronoa moves to intercept but...!
Spinning Tackle!
What?!
Ball man Sanji is sent flying skyward too!
Sanji!
Bringing up the rear is Big Pan!
He rushes for the falling Hamburg!
Punk Receive!
Hamburg catches Sanji above
enemy territory! Incredible!
They're within range of the ring!
Stupid Eyebrows!
Here it comes! The Hamburger Dunk!
Wh-What are you--?!
Zoro! Sanji! Do something!
Is it about to end already?!
Don't need to tell me...!
I ain't gonna... let 'em score!
You ain't gonna score!
I'm still in tip-top shape!
I can't let that damn swordsman snub me...
...by saving...
...my hide!
No goal!
It looks like ball man Sanji isn't going
to pass through the goal so easily!
Mind your own damn business!
You get thrown around too easy idiot!
A duo as powerful as the
Groggy Monsters has appeared!
We have an epic game on our hands!
This has never happened before!
This is unprecedented!
These behemoths were sent
flying through the air!
The crowd is stunned! Team Straw Hat is formidable!
I don't need you to give me backup!
It's only 'cause I can't count on you!
They're amazing!
They actually threw Pickles!
They sent Hamburg-san flying!
Who asked for your help?!
You get tossed around too much!
Oh no! What are you doing Hamburg?!
Lose and you'll regret it!
Oh but Team Straw Hat is acting strangely!
Although the game is still going
with both ball men in bounds
the two teammates are
arguing instead of playing!
They're funny!
Zoro! Sanji! You idiots!
What are you doing?! Now's your chance!
The other ball man's all alone!
Gang up on him and knock him into the ring!
Huh?
Big Pan goes in for a surprise attack!
Whoa...!
Too Bad Dance!
What are you running for?! He's the ball man!
Yeah we know! But hang on, he has blades under his shoes!
Hey, Ref!
What happened to "no weapons allowed"?!
Whoa! Can you be any more blatant?!
If he misses a play it's out of his hands!
Quit screwing around Ref!
Hold on Sanji-kun!
You saw the whole thing! Why are you sweatin' like a waterfall?!
I-I didn't s-see a th-thing...
Liar!
Hey hold on! He's the ref you know!
Yellow card to Sanji of Team Straw Hat!
Say what?!
W-Wait! Wait! Wait!
And there's the yellow warning card!
One more and Sanji the cook
will get a red ejection card!
I'll eject you!
I can't believe he's scummy enough to attack the referee!
Shut up! I oughta knock you off!
He's a gangster!
We gotta do something about his weapons...
Hold on! You're allowing that now?!
I just happen to be looking away...
Look out there, Ref!
That idiot's using an axe now! An axe!
No! Stop! You can't afford to get ejected!
Are you kidding me?! I can't let
'em get away with this insanity!
Don't you see?! They want you to get mad!
Pull yourself together!
This is for Chopper's sake!
All right! Then I'll beat him up!
Don't go complicating things!
Sanji-kun! Just beat 'em!
Pose of Love
You don't make any sense...
All right! Back to the game!
You didn't have to start with that again!
This is gettin' us nowhere!
But we can change our game plan
now that we know they've got weapons!
It's time to take him out!
Stay out of my way! I can handle him myself!
Work together! You're a team you know!
And there they go!
All three are about to collide!
Can't attack where his skin
is exposed! He's too slippery!
That leaves his hands
feet mask and trunks...
Loach Scooping Slide!
Crap!
Loach Racing Circus!
There it is! The Racing Circus acrobatics!
Both opponents slide across his wide back!
Ha! Won't work this time!
I can handle a little skating!
Now they can't escape!
So dizzy...!
Come on you guys!
Meanwhile the other two players
have gotten back into the game!
Oh! They're back in it!
Slaughter 'em!
Oh? Their attire is a little different now!
Hamburg, their leader is wearing iron knuckles and iron elbow guards!
Meanwhile Pickles has donned
spiked shoulder protectors!
These clearly violate the "no weapons" rule!
Oh, but the referee just happens
to have his back turned right now,
as he does some stretches!
Now I'm mad Leader!
Here goes!
Loach Coaster!
Everything's spinning...!
Let's do it Leader!
Yeah!
Spinning Tackle!
The recovered players counterattack!
But their target isn't the ball man... It's the swordsman Roronoa!
They're sniping him with the iron knuckles!
Hamburger Hammer!
Zoro!
The attack isn't over yet! Big Pan instantly takes an attack stance!
Hamburg prepares to use
his iron elbow guards!
No way!
It can't be...
This is truly dangerous! A horrifying combo!
He's almost like...
...an arrow!
Punk Attack!
Zoro!
It connects! Direct hit!
Note that deaths in Groggy Ring are
to be expected and are of no concern.
So... dizzy...
Team Foxy isn't ready to stop its attack yet!
Human...
Cannon!
Ugh... I feel sick...
The spiked shoulder protector draws near!
Sanji! Get out of the way!
Sling Tackle!
They're setting up Sanji the ball man now!
Size Attack: S!
Hamburg sends him flying back!
They're not preparing to score at all!
M!
L!
The Groggy Monsters unleash a spectacular team attack!
That's just terrible...
Zoro!
Sanji!
Looks like Team Straw Hat
isn't getting up from this!
Piece o' cake!
The opponents literally are "groggy"!
All that remains now is to stuff
the ball man into his ring coffin,
and this will be two wins in a row!
The undefeated Groggy Monsters
are supremely powerful!
We win again!
Hey cook...
Lend me a hand for ten seconds...
Sounds like... a reasonable length of time...
Hey! Look!
Wha...?!
They're up! Team Straw Hat is standing again!
Roronoa the swordsman and Sanji
the cook are terrifyingly tough!
They really know how to make a game exciting!
They're back up! Now get those jerks!
But do these two have
enough strength left to fight?!
Hey you guys...
One Monster Burger please!
Wh-What?!
What could that mean?
Our boss has just ordered a Monster Burger!
Hold on! They're clearly using weapons now!
Grind 'em up like a burger patty...
And slice 'em good like fresh pickles...
Who are the guests?!
Green lettuce... and yellow cheese!
Crush it all between big pans and you get...
...a Monster Burger!
There it is! Their utterly
horrific triple weapon attack!
There's no escape! Foul play
like this clearly calls for red cards!
Team Straw Hat is in a tough bind!
Oh, but wouldn't you know!
The ref just happens to have
his back turned as he stretches!
What are you doing?!
Stop Luffy!
But...!
They want us to butt in!
We need to grin and bear it Luffy!
Everything's set! The Groggy
Monsters commence their attack!
Whatever happens now don't blame me!
Naturally they go after Sanji the ball man!
Will he be ground up sliced
and crushed into a hamburger patty?!
I can't make much with
third-rate ingredients like you guys
but I'll cook each and every one of you!
You're mincemeat now!
Troisième...
Third Rate
He's fast!
...Haché!
Mincemeat
Bouquetiere...
Mixed Vegetables
...Shot!
Oh no!
Stop crushing!
Leader!
How dare you...?!
Don't forget this is a team battle.
Why you...!
I'll cut you up!
No-Sword Style...
...Dragon
...Twister
M-My word! Big Pan has fallen
victim to Pickles' spinning blades!
Oh no! Dammit...!
Bad Manner...
...Kick Course!
I-Incredible!
The gigantic Big Pan was falling over
but is now upright again!
A tremendous kick has kept
Big Pan on his feet and in a daze!
Oh! Now Zoro the swordsman charges in!
Naturally he's going after
Big Pan the ball man!
You're not getting past me!
I've had enough of you and the ref!
The crowd-- no the referee-- takes a direct hit!
That was on purpose...!
How dare he... hurt the ref...?!
Red card!
Huh?
My cards and whistle... They're gone...
You're a naughty girl.
Couldn't help it. It's an old habit of mine.
Oh! What's this?!
Is Team Straw Hat arguing again
in front of the lone Big Pan?!
Armée de l'Air Power Shoot!
Air Force Power Shoot
I-Incredible!
The gigantic wotan...
What?!
No way!
Big Pan...
is airborne!
Go!
They're headed for the goal ring!
No!
Goal!
Translation, FUNimation
Soundtracking, Halee
Infoboxes/Title Card, BernieCrane
Editing, Feeso
Quality Checking, Alasta, Galaxy 9000, Mr. Luffy
Timing, Galaxy 9000